vidmax.com 2012-05-24

# Funny Videos, Crazy Videos, Video Clips :: Vidmax.com

## Privacy Statement

Vidmax.com is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. 

Vidmax.com encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit.

Below is a summary of Vidmax.com online privacy policy. Types and uses of personal information. 

Your personal information is used in the following ways:

User IDs and Passwords. Provides you with access to your profile areas and to protected content. Account Information. These tell us more about who you are, how to contact you, and your shipping and billing information. Customer Feedback and Support. Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Vidmax.com. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs. Email Correspondence. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. 

We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage. 

## Third Party Advertising

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

Security measures. We protect the personal information you share with us.

Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so. 

## Data Retention

Vidmax.com will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

Linked web sites. 

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites. 

## Children's privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Vidmax.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer: Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. Check out the FTC's site(1) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 

We may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown. These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you. Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact.

## Third Party Advertising

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

Third Party Cookies. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
